[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these values signifies the greatest temperature?", "correct_answer": "One degree Celsius", "incorrect_answers": ["One degree Fahrenheit", "One degree Rankine", "One degree Kelvin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the squadron of blue-striped clone troopers that Darth Vader leads into the Jedi Temple?", "correct_answer": "501st Legion", "incorrect_answers": ["Royal Guards", "66th Infantry", "Imperial Guards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the star cluster that is also known as \u201cThe Seven Sisters\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Pleiades", "incorrect_answers": ["Bennekryse", "Arcturus", "Altair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the last name of Julie, the main character in the movie Valley Girl?", "correct_answer": "Richman", "incorrect_answers": ["Foreman", "Brent", "Bailey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the storm troopers blaster rifles called in the Star Wars movies?", "correct_answer": "E-11", "incorrect_answers": ["DC-15", "DL-44", "Thunderer heavy rifle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus has no natural satellite or moon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In nature adult jaguars are apex predators in the food chain. What does this mean?", "correct_answer": "They are not preyed on by other predators.", "incorrect_answers": ["They feed only on other predators.", "They do not hunt on other predators.", "Besides hunting they also feed on plants."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Seaman Hornsby in the film Operation Petticoat?", "correct_answer": "A Pig", "incorrect_answers": ["The Captian", "The supply officer", "A Nurse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Barbie.com is the number one girls site.  There are about this many visits to the site each month.", "correct_answer": "Over 8 million", "incorrect_answers": ["Over 2 million", "Over 1 million", "Over 5 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official name of Luxembourg?", "correct_answer": "Grand Duchy of Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["The Peoples Republic of Luxembourg", "The Luxembourg Democratic Republic", "The Kingdom of Luxembourg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some mammals are able to glide and parachute, but bats are the only ones capable of flying.  What is the name of the membrane that forms the surface of their wings?", "correct_answer": "Patagium", "incorrect_answers": ["Reticulum", "Corticulum", "Flagellum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is considered the best selling English-language novel of all times?", "correct_answer": "A Tale of Two Cities", "incorrect_answers": ["And Then There Were None", "The DaVinci Code", "The Hobbit"]}]